Max...
麦克斯...
Are you up?
你醒着吗
no .
没有
-Max,are you mad? -Yes.
-麦克斯 你还生气吗  -是的
-Are you up and mad? -No and yes.
-你是醒着还生气呢吗  -没有 是的
-your bed's so soft. -That's my boob.
-你的床真软啊  -那是我的咪咪
I know I moved out,but I came back.
我知道我搬出去了 但是我又回来了
I took the rest of our dead dream money
我拿破碎梦想里留下的钱
and bought some cocktails for myself and some people.And myself.
买了鸡尾酒给自己 和别人 然后自己
Did you bring me back any of those? 'Cause I can't listen to this sober.
有没有给我带杯回来 我可不想清醒地听你唠叨
Max...
麦克斯...
I have nothing.
我啥都没有
I really need the cupcake business.
真的很需要那个蛋糕生意
I can be different.
我可以变的
-No,you can't. -No,I can't.
-不 你没办法  -是 我改不了
But I can be better.
但是我能变好的
Please? Please,let's do this.
求你了 求你了 我们做生意吧
I know you have a fear of success.
我知道你恐惧成功
You do,because no one ever believed in your dreams.
你害怕 因为没人相信过你的梦想
But I believe in your dreams.
但是我相信
We have a dream.
我们有共同的梦